hi this is a quick demo on how to get
嗨，这是关于如何获得的快速演示
started with spring boot in Visual
从Visual中的Spring Boot开始
Studio code so the first thing we're
Studio代码，所以我们要做的第一件事
going to do here in Visual Studio code
在Visual Studio代码中将在此处执行
is install some extensions that will
正在安装一些扩展程序
help us work with spring boot projects
帮助我们处理Spring Boot项目
so I'm going to the marketplace and
所以我要去市场
search for spring and the thing I'm
寻找春天和我要的东西
gonna install is the spring boot
要安装的是弹簧靴
extension back from pivotal this will
从关键扩展回来这将
give you some spring boots specific
给你一些 spring boot
support for working in Java files as
支持以如下方式在Java文件中工作
well as boot properties and llamó file
以及启动属性和llamó文件
editing the other thing you get which is
编辑你得到的另一件事是
very useful is a wizard for quickly
一个非常有用的向导可以快速
generating projects using the spring
使用spring生成项目
initializer service so that's two things
初始化服务，这是两件事
that we want the other thing that we're
我们想要另一件事
going to install is some tooling to work
要安装是一些工作工具
with Java projects in general so I'm
与一般的Java项目，所以我
typing Java here and we're going to
在这里输入Java，我们将
install another extension part called
安装另一个扩展部分，称为
the Java extension back from Microsoft
从Microsoft返回的Java扩展
this pack will give you good Java
这个包会给你很好的Java
editing support from Red Hat as well as
来自Red Hat的编辑支持以及
a debugger which is the two things I'm
调试器，这是我要做的两件事
going to demo here there is a few other
要演示这里还有其他一些
things but I don't have time to go into
事情，但我没有时间去研究
ok that's good we've installed those
好的，我们已经安装了这些
let's reload these all these plugins
让我们重新加载所有这些插件
we've installed are now active that was
我们已经安装了，现在处于活动状态
easy
简单
and now I can start creating our
现在我可以开始创建我们的
projects so I'm just gonna do here
项目，所以我要在这里做
spring and choose the option to generate
春天并选择生成的选项
a new project I'll make a Java project I
一个新项目，我将创建一个Java项目
won't have to change much I'll just
不必做太多改变，我只是
change it here to hello world ok and we
将其更改为世界您好，我们
keep the version that was suggested I'm
保留建议的版本
gonna add a few starters the web starter
将要添加一些启动器Web启动器
because I'm gonna make a hello world web
因为我要打个世界网
app I'm gonna add dev tools because
应用，我要添加开发工具，因为
that's nice for debugging and restarting
非常适合调试和重新启动
quickly and the other thing I want is
很快，我想要的另一件事是
the actuator which will give us live
执行器，将带给我们生命
hovers in editor as you'll see later so
徘徊在编辑器中，稍后您将看到
that's very nice and I want that so here
很好，我想要，所以在这里
we go it's asking us where to save this
我们去问我们在哪里保存
I just take this folder here saying ok
我只是把这个文件夹放在这里说好
it asks me to open the project it just
它要求我打开项目
generated and we're good to go
产生，我们很高兴去
the project is ready too and here is my
项目也准备好了，这是我的
project once I go in here you can see
项目一旦我进入这里你就可以看到
that I for example have my
例如我有我的
support for editing properties files
支持编辑属性文件
like I said so I guess put something in
就像我说的，所以我想在里面放些东西
here for example like that and you have
例如这里，你有
hovers and editor things like support
悬停和编辑器之类的东西，如支持
which I don't have much time to demo so
我没有太多时间演示
let's do something else I'm gonna add a
让我们做点别的，我要加一个
request my thing so in these Java files
在这些Java文件中请求我的东西
get some spring boat specific things
得到一些春船特有的东西
like an a snippet to quickly generate a
像片段一样快速生成一个
request nothing I make that thing hello
我什么都没要求
world request nothing buy anything a few
世界什么都没要求买东西
things I'm just going to move this
我将要移动的东西
request
请求
keep things simple and just returns a
保持简单，只返回一个
message I need in control notation here
我在这里需要用控制符号表示的消息
and now my project is ready to run so
现在我的项目准备好运行了
let's put a breakpoint here because I
让我们在这里放一个断点，因为我
said we have a debugger and if I press
说我们有一个调试器，如果我按
f5 or go to this menu here I can start
f5或转到此菜单，我可以开始
the debugger the first time I do that it
第一次调试器
will generate launch configuration which
将生成启动配置
you might want to edit I don't need to
您可能需要编辑，我不需要
so I'll just close that again and press
所以我将再次关闭它，然后按
f5 again and this time it'll run for
再次按f5键，这次它将运行
real so now my application is starting
真实，所以现在我的应用程序开始了
you see the output here you see a few
你在这里看到输出，你看到一些
things which I mentioned earlier there
我在前面提到的东西
is this live hover information if you
这是实时悬停信息吗？
see this green thing that means there's
看到这绿色的东西，这意味着
something to hover and it will tell you
悬停的东西，它会告诉你
something about information in the
关于信息的一些东西
active processes that are related to
与之相关的活动过程
this piece of code for example here it
例如这段代码
says there is a request nothing in this
说没有任何要求
process which maps to this URL here so
在这里映射到该URL的过程
you might want to open that and for
您可能要打开它
convenience there is also a code lines
方便还有一条代码行
for that so if I click on this now
为此，如果我现在单击此
you'll see that the brows are quickly
你会看到眉毛很快
popped up browser pops up and open that
弹出的浏览器弹出并打开
URL and then I hit my breakpoint so
URL，然后我命中了断点
these debugger is now active I could
这些调试器现在处于活动状态，我可以
start with stepping and debugging this
从逐步调试开始
this is more or less where I wanted to
这大概是我想要的地方
end my demo I hope you enjoyed it and
结束我的演示，希望您喜欢它，并且
thanks for watching
谢谢收看
you
您